Jun Hwang

Fairfax, Virginia

junhwang77@hotmail.com | (408) 507-7296

Github: https://github.com/junhwang77/Jun-s-Repository

AWS: http://54.202.90.47/

Technical Skills

Front-End Development

HTML5

CSS3

jQuery / JavaScript

Languages

PHP Python

Databases

MySQL SQLite

Servers

Apache

Frameworks

Django Codelgniter Twitter Bootstrap

Version Control

Github

Methodology

OOP MVC

RESTful Architecture

Full Stack Web Developer

Recent graduate from Coding Dojo Bootcamp, experienced in LAMP stack, Python, and front-end web development. I am currently residing in Davis, CA, and am in the process of relocating to Fairfax, Virginia in June 12th of this year.

Education

Coding Dojo – Online

(Oct 2016 - April 2017)

Full Stack Web Development Program, Black Belt

Completed 20 weeks online program, learning front-end development, Python stack, and LAMP stack.

University of California, Davis

(Sept 2009 -June 2013)

Bachelor of Science in Animal Science, Laboratory Animal emphasis.

Projects

User Dashboard App A simple Facebook like application, allowing the users to add messages for other users, which can also be commented. Admin user can create/edit/delete other user accounts, and also give admin access to them. Created database schema along with controllers and models for fully functional app.

Tech used - PHP Codeigniter, Apache, MySQL, Twitter Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS3

Quotable Quotes Application that allows users to register and login to create quotes into database and add them to their favorite list. Created database schema along with controllers and models for fully functional app, and deployed using AWS (Amazon Web Services), within 4.5 hours for the PHP belt exam.

Tech used - PHP, Codelgniter, Apache, MySQL, Twitter Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS3

Wish List Application that allows users to register and login, and create items and add them to their personal wish list. Created database schema along with controllers and models for a fully functional app.

Tech used - PHP, Codelgniter, Apache, MySQL, Twitter Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS3

Travel App A basic application that allows the user to login and create trips, which also allows other users to join in by adding it to their own trip list.

Tech used - Python, Django, SQLite, HTML5, CSS3

Other Experiences

UC Davis Veterinary Medical Teaching Hospital – Davis, CA Anatomy Lab Assistant III

(Jul 2014 – Oct 2016)

- -Maintained and stocked laboratory inventory using Google spread sheet.
- -Worked with faculties to prepare lab classes and assist them in facilitating lab classes.
- -Designed and created laboratory map layout templates and sign posters, using Photoshop.
- -Researched and purchased lab equipment and chemicals that dramatically improved specimen storage and maintenance.

Jackson Laboratory – Sacramento, CA Animal Care Technician

(Aug 2013 – July 2014)

- -Followed strict Standard Operating Procedures for the bio-security of the rooms and mice husbandry.
- -Quality checked individual mice, and packed them from inventories to be shipped out to research laboratories
- -Used Windows NT handhelds, to input data for mice birth, death, culling, disease identification, shipping, and cage transfers.

UC Davis Larson Lab – Davis, CA Undergraduate Researcher / Assistant

(Mar 2011 – Mar 2012)

- -Used MATlab program to input data and conduct global analysis of the team's collected data.
- -Graphically illustrated experimented proteins (phytochromes) on Visual Molecular Dynamics software.

UC Davis Koinonia Christian Fellowship Club – Davis, CA Alumni Staff Volunteer / Member

(Aug 2009 - Present)

Actively participated in organizing on-campus events and social gatherings, including New Student Welcome Night, with attendance of 700+ new incoming UC Davis freshmen and junior transfers -Actively participated in hosting Project Angel Tree, Valentines Day of Compassion at the Salvation army Shelter, Convalescent Home visits and Freshmen Dorm Moo-ve in day. -Volunteer bassist, guitarist, drummer, sound setup crew, and cook.